now that we have seen how tlbs work
let's do a quiz on tlb performance
suppose we have a program with a 1
Megabyte array that it reads one bite at
a time from start to end and this start
to end read happens 10 times so 10 times
we sweep through the array reading it
suppose also that no other memory other
than this 1 megab array is accessed
during this time suppose that the
processor has a 4 kiloby Page size and a
level one tlb that has 100 28 entries
and the level two tlb with 1024 entries
and the tlbs are initially empty they
have no translations cached when we
begin the first read the array here is
Page aligned meaning the array begins at
the beginning of a page and the tlb is a
direct map the question for you is in
the level one tlb we have how many hits
and how many misses and in the level two
be how many hits and how many misses